(Sheldon-bot :)I must speak to him.
(Leonard:)Of course you must.
(Penny:)You know, there's an
Olive Garden down the street.
(Penny:)You guys should try it sometime.
(Sheldon-bot :)Excuse me,
Mr. Wozniak?
(Steve Wozniak:)Oh, hey.
(Steve Wozniak:)Nice virtual presence device.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Sheldon-bot :)I just want to say
I'm a big fan.
You're my 15th favorite
technological visionary.
Only 15th?
(Sheldon-bot :)It's still six spots
above Steve Jobs.
(Sheldon-bot :)I care neither for turtlenecks
(Sheldon-bot :)nor showmanship.
(Steve Wozniak:)Yeah, I never got
that turtleneck thing.
(Sheldon-bot :)One of my proudest possessions
is a vintage 1977 Apple Two.
(Sheldon-bot :)Despite the file system
limitations of Apple DOS 3.3,
(Sheldon-bot :)it was a pretty nifty
little achievement.
(Steve Wozniak:)Thanks, we were shooting
for "nifty."
(Steve Wozniak:)You know, if you had it here,
(Steve Wozniak:)I'd autograph it for you.
(Sheldon-bot:)Don't move
for 15 to 30 minutes,
(Sheldon-bot:)depending on how
the buses are running.